Finding aid of the Herbert Hutchinson Brimley Photograph Collection, 1880-1977 PHC.42
State Archives of North Carolina
- Numbererd, PhC.42.OvsBox4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Plant, n.d. Naval Stores? Tarp plant? Pumping Plant, PhC.42.OvsBox4.47; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - "Mountain Stream and Water Mill Frame,", PhC.42.OvsBox4.48; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - "University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill, NC, Old West, Memorial Hall, and New West, "ca. 1890., PhC.42.OvsBox4.5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - "Western Mountain Valley," McDowell Co., NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.OvsBox4.7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - "Venerable Scuppernongs," Grape Vineyard, Eastern, NC, 1890., PhC.42.OvsBox4.9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Color, PhC.42.OvsBox5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - "Shipping Cotton," New Bern, NC, n.d., PhC.42.OvsBox5.1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Man standing in a field of corn and bean vines, n.d., PhC.42.OvsBox5.10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Interior of Mountain Apple House Yancey County, PhC.42.OvsBox5.11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Watermelon Vine with Thirty Six Melons Wake County, Grown on Side of Old Haystack, PhC.42.OvsBox5.12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Dairy Cow in Field, n.d., PhC.42.OvsBox5.2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - "Corn and Beans," near New Bern, NC, n.d., PhC.42.OvsBox5.3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Cornfield and Haystacks, Rural Western, NC, n.d., PhC.42.OvsBox5.4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Corn and Beans Near New Bern, PhC.42.OvsBox5.5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Pear Orchard Geo. N Ives- Newport, PhC.42.OvsBox5.6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Grade Shorpshire Sheep RW Scott- Haw River, PhC.42.OvsBox5.7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Percheron Horse RW Scott- Haw River, PhC.42.OvsBox5.8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Velvet Beans Edgecombe Test Farm, PhC.42.OvsBox5.9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Miscellaneous, PhC.42.OvsBox6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - "Partial View, A and M College West Raleigh, North Carolina," n.d. (N.83.3.37), PhC.42.OvsBox6.1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - "View from Dalton Station," Stokes County, Five miles distant, S. L. Alderman, Greensboro, NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.OvsBox6.10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - "View from Pinnacle Station," Stokes County, of Pilot Mountain, Surry County, Two miles distant, S. L. Alderman, Greensboro, NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.OvsBox6.11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - "View from Base of a Mountain," (Pilot Mountain), Three Quarters of a mile, S. L. Alderman, Greensboro, NC, ca. 1890s., PhC.42.OvsBox6.12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Group of unidentified men pose in front of an unidentified residence, n.d., PhC.42.OvsBox6.13; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - "The Campus and Buildings, Wake Forest, "ca. 1900., PhC.42.OvsBox6.14; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Elevated View of Mt. Airy, Surry County, NC, ca. 1900., PhC.42.OvsBox6.15; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified ship anchored and tied at an unidentified wharf, n.d., copy print by Chartley Photo Services, Newport, NC, 1972., PhC.42.OvsBox6.16; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Exhibitors pose in front of a building which housed the N.C. Exhibit at Jamestown, VA, 1907., PhC.42.OvsBox6.17; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified beach scene with nets drying, n.d.(N.83.6.183), PhC.42.OvsBox6.18; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - "State Normal School," Greensboro, NC, n.d., PhC.42.OvsBox6.2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - "State Normal School," Greensboro, NC, n.d. (?), PhC.42.OvsBox6.3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Rocky Mount's First Tobacco Trailer attached to a Model "T", Rocky Mount, NC, 1913, owner G. G. Viverette, Halifax County, NC., PhC.42.OvsBox6.4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - "Rock Quarry in operation", (Greystone Quarries near Raleigh), Raleigh, NC, n.d. (M-12), PhC.42.OvsBox6.5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Visitors to Jamestown Exposition, 1906 (1907)., PhC.42.OvsBox6.6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - View of an Exhibit (Probably North Carolinas), Chicago Exposition, 1904., PhC.42.OvsBox6.7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Agriculture Building during a parade, Raleigh, NC, ca. 1910s., PhC.42.OvsBox6.8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Iroquois Axe of French Manufacture, St. Regis, NY, R. B. Hough, 1879., PhC.42.OvsBox6.9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Miscellaneous, PhC.42.OvsBox7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Photo Collage containing 15 Prints of J. I. Wyatt's Granite Quarry at Faith, NC, ca. 1900., PhC.42.OvsBox7-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Dam and Power Plant, n.d., PhC.42.OvsBox7-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Cape Hatteras Lighthouse, Cape Hatteras, NC, n.d., PhC.42.OvsBox7-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified Rural Landscape, n.d., PhC.42.OvsBox7-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - "Toxaway Lake Region," Transylvania Co., NC, n.d., PhC.42.OvsBox7-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Catch of two fish by Le Roy, ca. 1896. (Color), PhC.42.OvsBox7-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Catch of two fish by Le Roy, ca. 1896. (Color), PhC.42.OvsBox7-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Cranberry Iron Mine, Avery County, NC, PhC.42.OvsBox7-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - North Carolina Pulp Co., Plymouth, NC, n.d., PhC.42.OvsBox7-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Scenic Mountain View, n.d., PhC.42.OvsBox7-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946